

I create the best possible experience for web and software applications based on the goals of the business and the needs of the end user. I'm fascinated by watching people use the products I design and I immediately begin to think of ways to make helpful improvements. Learning is a passion of mine and I often spend my spare time discovering new web technologies and figuring out how I can apply them into my current projects.

EXPERIENCE

August 2014 - July 2017

ResponseTek

User Experience Designer

- Prototyped design concepts and tested them on our application users.
- Turned visual designs into working HTML/CSS/JS prototypes.
- Organized and ran product usability tests both live and remote.
- Created and presented user flows.
- Researched and designed user personas that have been adopted by the entire company.
- Developed and maintained great working relationships with the development team.
- Designed various data visualizations for new reports within our application.

September 2009 - June 2014

Brandspank Retailer Marketing

User Experience Designer, Project Manager and Digital Strategist

- Created both static and interactive wireframes and sitemaps for full client websites and applications.
- Presented wireframes and ideas to internal and external stakeholders to get project buy-in.
- Managed the development process for email marketing campaigns that were responsive.
- Created A/B tests for email marketing campaigns and decided on the elements that should be tested.
- Managed different approaches to mobile for business; unique mobile site, responsive site and mobile applications.
- Experience dealing with various types of web technologies and defining how they can be applied to the clients business.
- Directed and managed the interactive resources on various client campaign projects that use; digital media, mobile, social, email & applications.

EDUCATION

2007 - 2009

Creative Advertising Diploma - May 2009 Seneca College - The School of Communication Arts

SKILLS

Sketch, InvisionApp, HTML/CSS/JS, Adobe Creative Suite, Data Visualization, Usability Testing.